{
    "pokemonId201": {
        "nationalNo": 201,
        "name": "Unown",
        "types": [
            "psychic"
        ],
        "genderRatio": {
            "male": 0,
            "female": 0
        },
        "genderDifference": "",
        "species": "Symbol Pok√©mon",
        "description": "When alone, nothing happens. However, if there are two or more, an odd power is said to emerge.",
        "region": [],
        "height": "0.5",
        "weight": "5",
        "abilities": {
            "normal": [
                "Levitate"
            ],
            "hidden": []
        },
        "pvpTier": "Untiered",
        "evYields": [
            "+1 Attack",
            "+1 Sp. Attack"
        ],
        "eggGroups": [
            "Cannot Breed"
        ],
        "baseStats": {
            "hp": 48,
            "attack": 72,
            "defense": 48,
            "spAttack": 72,
            "spDefense": 48,
            "speed": 48
        },
        "moves": [
            {
                "level": "START",
                "moveId": "moveId196"
            },
            {
                "level": "TM",
                "moveId": "moveId196"
            }
        ],
        "forms": {
            "?": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Monean Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-qm-n-front",
                        "back": "201-qm-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-qm-s-front",
                        "back": "201-qm-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "A": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Monean Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-a-n-front",
                        "back": "201-a-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-a-s-front",
                        "back": "201-a-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "C": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Liptoo Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-c-n-front",
                        "back": "201-c-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-c-s-front",
                        "back": "201-c-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "D": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Liptoo Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-d-n-front",
                        "back": "201-d-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-d-s-front",
                        "back": "201-d-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "H": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Liptoo Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-h-n-front",
                        "back": "201-h-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-h-s-front",
                        "back": "201-h-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "O": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Liptoo Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-o-n-front",
                        "back": "201-o-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-o-s-front",
                        "back": "201-o-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "U": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Liptoo Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-u-n-front",
                        "back": "201-u-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-u-s-front",
                        "back": "201-u-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "E": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Weepth Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-e-n-front",
                        "back": "201-e-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-e-s-front",
                        "back": "201-e-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "I": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Weepth Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-i-n-front",
                        "back": "201-i-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-i-s-front",
                        "back": "201-i-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "N": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Weepth Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-n-n-front",
                        "back": "201-n-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-n-s-front",
                        "back": "201-n-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "S": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Weepth Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-s-n-front",
                        "back": "201-s-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-s-s-front",
                        "back": "201-s-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "J": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Dilford Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-j-n-front",
                        "back": "201-j-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-j-s-front",
                        "back": "201-j-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "L": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Dilford Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-l-n-front",
                        "back": "201-l-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-l-s-front",
                        "back": "201-l-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "P": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Dilford Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-p-n-front",
                        "back": "201-p-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-p-s-front",
                        "back": "201-p-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "Q": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Dilford Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-q-n-front",
                        "back": "201-q-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-q-s-front",
                        "back": "201-q-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "R": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Dilford Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-r-n-front",
                        "back": "201-r-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-r-s-front",
                        "back": "201-r-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "F": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Scufib Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-f-n-front",
                        "back": "201-f-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-f-s-front",
                        "back": "201-f-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "G": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Scufib Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-g-n-front",
                        "back": "201-g-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-g-s-front",
                        "back": "201-g-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "K": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Scufib Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-k-n-front",
                        "back": "201-k-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-k-s-front",
                        "back": "201-k-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "T": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Scufib Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-t-n-front",
                        "back": "201-t-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-t-s-front",
                        "back": "201-t-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "Y": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Scufib Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-y-n-front",
                        "back": "201-y-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-y-s-front",
                        "back": "201-y-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "B": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Rixy Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-b-n-front",
                        "back": "201-b-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-b-s-front",
                        "back": "201-b-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "M": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Rixy Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-m-n-front",
                        "back": "201-m-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-m-s-front",
                        "back": "201-m-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "V": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Rixy Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-v-n-front",
                        "back": "201-v-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-v-s-front",
                        "back": "201-v-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "W": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Rixy Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-w-n-front",
                        "back": "201-w-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-w-s-front",
                        "back": "201-w-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "X": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Rixy Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-x-n-front",
                        "back": "201-x-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-x-s-front",
                        "back": "201-x-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "!": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Viapois Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-em-n-front",
                        "back": "201-em-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-em-s-front",
                        "back": "201-em-s-back"
                    }
                }
            },
            "Z": {
                "locations": [
                    {
                        "type": "cave",
                        "region": "Kanto",
                        "location": "Viapois Chamber",
                        "levels": "25",
                        "rarity": "very common"
                    }
                ],
                "sprites": {
                    "normal": {
                        "front": "201-z-n-front",
                        "back": "201-z-n-back"
                    },
                    "shiny": {
                        "front": "201-z-s-front",
                        "back": "201-z-s-back"
                    }
                }
            }
        }
    }
}